Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**  
Downline Farm values your privacy and is committed to protecting it.

**1\. Collection of your information**

The only information we collect **directly** from you is the information you enter on your registration form. Other information may be collected indirectly, which is rather typical of most websites. For instance, your IP address and the source that referred you to our website are generally known. 

We use third-party companies that may collect certain information when you visit our web site. These companies may utilize cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use **non-personally identifiable** information.  The companies we are referring to here are the AddThis Social Media Sharing App, and Viral Nugget, a third party advertiser whose ads appear on our pages. These third party companies do not get access to your personal information.

We do not collect ANY information related to your payment processing, credit card or bank account. The entire payment transaction is carried out at the payment processor’s website.

**2\. Sharing of your information**

We do not sell, or transfer Personally Identifiable Information.

The person who sponsored you will automatically receive your name and email address upon your registration.  We work as a team, so it is vital that your sponsor has your contact information. We will also provide members that you sponsor with your name and email address upon their request.

Third party companies may share non-personally identifiable information.

To learn more about the privacy policies of the third party companies visit:

**AddThis**: [https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/addthis-privacy-policy.html](https://www.oracle.com/legal/privacy/addthis-privacy-policy.html)

**Viral Nugget:** [http://www.viralnugget.com/members/terms.php](http://www.viralnugget.com/members/terms.php)

**3.** **Links to Other Websites:**

This web site contains links to other websites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are moving to another web site, which we are not directly associated with. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites as their privacy policies may differ from ours.

© 2024 Downline Farm all rights reserved worldwide
